asiarooms.com 2015-09-05

# 

You agree that financial compensation alone may not be adequate for us if there is a breach or threatened breach of our Terms and that we are entitled to seek all remedies available to us.  Each right or remedy of you and us in respect of these Terms shall not affect any other right or remedy of us whether under these Terms or otherwise. The rights and remedies provided under this agreement are in addition to, and not exclusive of, any rights or remedies provided by law. 

In the event that any provision of these Terms is found by a court or administrative body to be unenforceable, that provision shall not be a part of these Terms and the remaining provisions shall continue to apply. 

Nothing under the Terms shall give rights to any person who is not a party to it (whether under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999) or otherwise. 

If you or LateRooms waive any rights in result of a breach or default under, any part of these Terms by the other will not be deemed a waiver of any subsequent breach or default. Further it will not affect the other Terms unless expressly confirmed in writing by the party waiving its rights. 

LateRooms reserves the right to change our Terms at any time. We shall post such updated Terms on our Site and your continued use of our Site shall be deemed acceptance of such updated Terms. 

Our Site booking services are available in English, Spanish, French, Italian and German. The original English version of these Terms may have been translated into other languages. The translated versions of these Terms are provided as a courtesy and for information purposes only.  In the event of a dispute or conflict between the English version of these Terms and any other language versions, the English version shall prevail and shall be conclusive and binding.  The English version shall be used in legal proceedings.  

## Website Terms and Conditions

### General

"LateRooms" means Late Rooms Limited, a private limited company which is a subsidiary of TUI AG with registered number 03816947 of TUI Travel House, Crawley Business Quarter, Fleming Way, Crawley, West Sussex, RH10 9QL, England.  Our VAT registration number is 849 747 171.  LateRooms acts as a booking agent for the hotels and other service providers advertised on the websites www.laterooms.com and www.laterooms.com.au (the "Site"). In these Terms references to ‘we’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’ are references to LateRooms and references to ‘you’ or ‘your’ are references to Site users and/or visitors. 

By using, browsing and/or visiting the Site (either via a mobile, desktop or any other platform including personal tablets) you acknowledge that you have read and agree to these Website Terms of Use, our Booking Terms and Conditions, and our Privacy and Cookie Policy ("the Terms") and you expressly consent and agree to be bound by the Terms, as may be amended from time to time, and all applicable laws and regulations that govern this Site and your booking. 

Please take a moment to familiarise yourself with our Terms before using the Site. They may have been amended since your last visit. Your attention is drawn in particular to the section below called ‘Our Liability’. If you do not agree to our Terms please do not visit our Site. 

References to "accommodation providers" means the owner/providers of the hotels, apartments, villas and other accommodation of any description featured on this Site and "accommodation" means the accommodation including all facilities and services advertised on our Site that we have agreed to arrange in connection with your confirmed booking. 

Affiliates are third parties who, in agreement with LateRooms distribute LateRooms accommodation to their customers. 

### Access to our Site

LateRooms grants you access to our Site on a temporary basis. We may change the arrangements for access to, or even withdraw access to our Site on a temporary or permanent basis at some point in the future and reserve the right to do so, without telling you in advance. 

Because of the nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee that our Site will be uninterrupted or that you will always be able to gain reliable access to our Site and we make no guarantees as to its operation, functionality or otherwise.   It remains your responsibility for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to our Site. 

### Terms of Use and Site Use

LateRooms may suspend access to the Site, due to maintenance, security reasons or force majeure with no obligation to reimburse or compensate you for the period in which access was suspended. Access to the Site is strictly controlled by LateRooms and LateRooms reserves the right to change, modify, substitute or suspend or remove without notice, any information or service from time to time. 

LateRooms is the owner or licensee of all intellectual property rights on our Site and in material published on it, including the “look and feel” of our Site. These rights are protected by laws and treaties around the world including, but not limited to copyright, design rights, database rights and trade mark laws.  

LateRooms is the owner of several trademarks. Except where permitted by applicable law, these Terms of Use and Site Use, or otherwise set out on our Site, you may not use such trade marks without our prior written permission. 

Other than personally identifiable information or sensitive information, which is covered under the Privacy Policy, any material you transmit or post to LateRooms shall be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. 

You may save one short cut desktop link on your computer, tablet, mobile or other device, to our Site [homepage](http://www.laterooms.com.au/) . 

You may download one copy of Site content for your own personal and non-commercial use but you may not remove any trademark, copyright or other proprietary notice. You may not otherwise copy, modify, reproduce, sell, lease, market or distribute the content placed on the Site without the prior written consent of LateRooms. You must not use illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics from our Site separately from any accompanying text. You must not remove any indications of ownership from any materials which came from our Site. Where there are no indications of ownership you must acknowledge our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of the material and must not claim it as your own or as that of another. You may only use this Site to make legitimate enquiries or bookings for yourself or another person for whom you are legally authorised to act. 

You shall not:

\-  post, transmit or disseminate any information on or via this Site which is or may be harmful, obscene, threatening, deceptive, degrading, defamatory or otherwise illegal, or may cause an infringement of the rights of any other; 

\-  make any other unauthorised, false or fraudulent booking; 

\-  make any bookings or reservations on this Site with the purpose of reselling such booking or reservation to or for the benefit of a third party; 

\-  use any software, routine or device to interfere or attempt to interfere electronically or manually with the operation or functionality of this Site including, but not limited to, uploading or making available files containing corrupt data or viruses via whatever means; 

\-  deface, alter or interfere with the appearance and layout of this Site, any documents or materials which appear on our Site or the underlying software code; 

\-  take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on this Site or related infrastructure; 

\-  use the whole or any part of our Site or its contents for any commercial or money-making purpose; 

\-  access parts of the Site which are not intended for public use; 

\-  attempt to disrupt or interfere with our Site in any way or with another person’s use of our Site, or use our Site as a means of disrupting or interfering with other Sites; 

\-  probe, scan or test the vulnerability of our Site or any network connected to it; 

\-  use any device to obtain any personal or confidential information through our Site; 

\-  impersonate any person or entity or misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity; 

\-  deep-link to, copy, monitor, display, download or reproduce any part of our Site (without our express permission to do so). 

All of the above are forbidden regardless of the means used, including but not limited to, hacking or by the introduction of any worms, Trojans, viruses, unauthorised, malicious or harmful code or other harmful software. Some of the acts described above may be criminal acts under the Computer Misuse Act 1990. 

Without prejudice to any of LateRooms's other rights, LateRooms reserves the right to deny access to this Site and/or cancel bookings and/or remove any postings or material uploaded by you to our Site and/or take legal proceedings against you for the reimbursement of all costs wherever and whenever LateRooms believes (at LateRooms’s absolute discretion) that you are in breach of any of the LateRooms Terms. In certain circumstances we may also give information to law enforcement authorities. 

### Site content

LateRooms may modify the content of the Site and/or Terms at any time, and such modification shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified content and/or Terms on the Site and your continued use of or access to this Site will be deemed to indicate your acceptance of the modified content and/or Terms. 

We use reasonable efforts to ensure that our Site is free of viruses, however, because of the nature of the internet and viruses and similar malicious code, we cannot and do not guarantee that it is. Please take care and remember it is your responsibility to protect your computer, tablet or mobile device against viruses and ensure that you log off shared computers after use. It is always wise for you to run an anti-virus programme on all content and materials downloaded from the Internet in general and the Site in particular. 

LateRooms is not responsible for pricing, typographical, or other errors on its Site.   

### Your Privacy

Retaining your trust is a responsibility that we take very seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our Site visitors. Our [Privacy Policy](http://www.laterooms.com.au/en/static/TermsOfUse.mvc#s4)  sets out what personal information we collect about you, how we will use it, and how we will protect it. 

### Links and Downloads

LateRooms may provide hyperlinks or pointers to other websites maintained by third parties which LateRooms think may be of interest to visitors of the Site. Such other websites are not under the control of LateRooms or maintained by LateRooms and we are not responsible for the content of such websites. LateRooms provides these links for your convenience only but does not monitor or endorse the material on them. LateRooms cannot accept any liability whatsoever and howsoever arising in relation to any such other websites (including, by way of example, any inability to access or delay in accessing any such other website) or in relation to any material or information appearing on them or which you may otherwise come across after leaving the Site by way of a hypertext link or any other means or for any services or facilities of any description which you may book through or via any such website. 

### Your Account

You must provide a valid email address and any other information requested during the account signup process in order to obtain an account. You must ensure that all account information remains complete and accurate. When your Account has been created you will be able to access it from any platform (i.e. via the Site, our App or via Mobile Access). If you choose to access your Account on the App, our App Terms and Conditions will apply when you download and use the App. 

You are responsible for all activities conducted using your account or user details. Please let us know as soon as possible if you think someone is making or might make unauthorised use of your account or user details.  LateRooms may in its own discretion monitor your account from time to time and may permanently or temporarily disable accounts at any time. 

We may also permanently or temporarily disable your account, or issue you with a new account or user details, if we know of or suspect any actual or potential breach of security. 

### Mobile Access

This section applies when you access our Site using a mobile or tablet application such as a version of this Site optimised for use on mobile or tablet devices ("Mobile Access "). If you do not agree to be bound by this section of our Terms you may not use or access the Mobile Access facilities and should, if applicable, delete any mobile or tablet application used for Mobile Access. 

Mobile Access is data intensive.  You are responsible for any carrier or other data charges incurred when using Mobile Access and LateRooms will not be liable for any charges you incur.  We recommend you check with your network provider if you are unsure of the charges that may apply. 

Mobile Access will use your device's cellular and/or Wi-Fi connection to synchronise content on the Mobile Access with the information on our Site. 

LateRooms has no control over your device's network connection, and we therefore cannot represent or warrant that any information (including accommodation availability and prices) is correct or up to date. In the event of any discrepancy, content and prices published on the Site will take precedence. 

 Mobile Access is only available in English.

### Our Liability

**Your attention is particularly drawn to this section.**

Nothing in these terms shall, nor shall be deemed to exclude our liability for any death or personal injury caused as a result of our negligence, or the negligence of our employees or for fraudulent misrepresentation. 

Subject to the preceding paragraph LateRooms shall not be liable for any losses, expenses or damages of any sort due to you as a result of the acts, errors, omissions, breaches, negligence, fraudulent intent, misleading or untrue statements, wilful misconduct or any other tortious act attributable either wholly or in part to accommodation providers or any other independent business which includes their employees, directors, officers, agents, representatives or any other person connected to them.  

While we will use reasonable care and skill to ensure that the information provided on our Site is accurate, no guarantees for the accuracy of information are made. LateRooms’s website including information relating to products and services (or to third party affiliate information, products and services), is provided ‘as is’. It is provided without any representation or endorsement made and without warranty of any kind, whether express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement, compatibility, security and accuracy. 

LateRooms shall not be liable for any damages arising as a result of any inaccurate information or errors on our Site relating to accommodation information, including but not limited to details of accommodation providers and their availability of rooms, price of accommodation, accommodation facilities, any accreditations afforded to the information and/or service providers who are independent businesses and are not agents or employees of LateRooms and or any of its  group companies. 

LateRooms shall not be liable to you for any losses in the event of accommodation providers overbooking, cancelling of bookings in full or in part, force majeure events or any other cause beyond our or their control. We act only as an information provider. 

LateRooms will not be liable to you for any of the following: 

•  Because the information you put into our Site is inaccurate or incomplete; 

•  Because we have changed the arrangement for access to, denied you access to or closed or suspended our Site; 

•  Because of interrupted and/or unreliable access to our Site or because you cannot use our Site at any time where the cause is beyond our reasonable control; 

•  Because you have connected to any linked third party websites; 

•  Because you have breached our Terms;  

•  Any unauthorised access to or loss of personal information that is beyond our reasonable control or where we have not been negligent; 

•  Because of a distributed denial-of-service attack, viruses or other technologically harmful material that infects your computer, tablet or mobile device, computer programs, data or other items because you used our Site or downloaded material from it. 

LateRooms shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special or consequential damages, nor any loss of profit, loss of production, loss of revenue, or damage to goodwill or reputation arising out of, or in any way connected with, your use of this Site or with your inability to use this Site. 

### Accessibility and navigating this website

LateRooms takes responsibility for making accessible web content and software seriously. LateRooms is committed to developing software products that promote accessibility for people with disabilities and meet current accessibility standards, including those defined by Section 508 website of the U.S. Rehabilitation Act and the W3C's Web Content Accessibility Guidelines. 

LateRooms is actively engaged in the ongoing process of testing our products and Site for compliance with current accessibility standards 1.0. 

At LateRooms we are working hard to provide access to services and information that are helpful to all our customers. Many Internet users with disabilities find web sites difficult to use simply because of the way they are designed. This Site has been designed to be as accessible as possible and to be compatible with the types of adaptive technology used by people with disabilities, including screen readers. 

On this Site you can control the size of the text, the colours and the style sheets, dependent upon the functionality of your browser. 

To navigate through this Site once you have gone beyond the homepage, please use the menu at the top of each page. 

You may change the font size of this document to your preference through your browser by doing the following:- 

(a) In Internet Explorer, select View, then Text Size, and then your preferred size; or 

(b) If you are using an alternative browser, please refer to the specific browser instructions. 

You may import your own style sheet into this Site by doing the following:-. 

(a) In Internet Explorer select tools, then Internet Options, and then accessibility. Next click on any or all of three checkboxes to ignore colours, font styles or font sizes. In the same window you can change your stylesheet by clicking the checkbox that says, 'format document using my stylesheet' then simply browse to your style sheet and click ok; 

 or

(b) If you are using an alternative browser, please refer to the specific browser instructions. 

We have tested this Site thoroughly and are always keen to improve our accessibility tools. We would like to know if you have found this Site accessible or if you have had any problems. Please email admin@laterooms.com with any queries or comments or call (+44) (0) 870 735 0279. 

### Legislation and Courts of Jurisdiction

These Terms will be governed by English law and any disputes will be dealt with exclusively by the English courts. 

If the Site is accessed outside of England we make no representation that the Site or its content is available or otherwise suitable for use outside England. Should you choose to access or use the Site outside England this is entirely at your own risk, and you shall be responsible for (1) ensuring that what you are doing in your country of origin is legal; and (2) the consequences and compliance by you with all applicable laws, regulations, byelaws, codes of practice, licences, registrations, permits and authorisations (including any laws that relate to businesses providing services). 

### Miscellaneous

Our Site booking services are available in English, Spanish, French, Italian and Dutch. The original English version of these Terms may have been translated into other languages. The translated versions of these Terms are provided as a courtesy and for information purposes only.  In the event of a dispute or conflict between the English version of these Terms and any other language versions, the English version shall prevail and shall be conclusive and binding.  The English version shall be used in legal proceedings. 

You agree that financial compensation alone may not be adequate for us if there is a breach or threatened breach of our Terms and that we are entitled to seek all remedies available to us.  Each right or remedy of you and us in respect of these Terms shall not affect any other right or remedy of us whether under these Terms or otherwise. 

In the event that any provision of these Terms is found by a court or administrative body to be unenforceable, that provision shall not be a part of these Terms and the remaining provisions shall continue to apply. 

LateRooms shall not be responsible if we are unable to perform our obligations due to events which are genuinely beyond our reasonable control. 

Nothing under the Terms shall give rights to any person who is not a party to it (whether under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999) or otherwise. 

If you or LateRooms waive any rights in result of a breach or default under, any part of these Terms by the other will not be deemed a waiver of any subsequent breach or default. Further it will not affect the other Terms unless expressly confirmed in writing by the party waiving its rights. 

LateRooms reserves the right to change our Terms at any time. We shall post such updated Terms on our Site and your continued use of our Site shall be deemed acceptance of such updated Terms. 

## Laterooms Privacy Policy

We understand that making purchases online involves your trust. Retaining your trust is a responsibility that we take very seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

By disclosing your personal information to us by using our website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information as stated in this policy. 

The personal information that we collect from you shall be obtained, processed and transmitted in compliance with applicable data protection legislation. Since our servers are located in the United Kingdom, the personal information that we collect from you shall be obtained, processed and transmitted in compliance with European Directives 95/46 and 2002/58, as well as any other such legislation that replaces, substitutes, complements and develops it such as the Data Protection Act 1998 from the United Kingdom. 

"Personal Information" means information that relates to a living individual who can be identified from that information or from that information together with other information which is held by or is likely to be held by us. 

### (1) What personal information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information: 

  * information that you provide by filling in any booking forms or other forms on our website or which you give us over the telephone, including your name, (home or office) address, date of birth, (business or private) email address, (mobile, home or office) telephone number, credit card details (i.e. credit card type and number, CVC code, expiration date, credit card holder name) and to the extent available, reservation preferences and smoking preferences; 
  * information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including where you have clicked on any of our advertising links or banners, (including your IP address, geographical location, browser/platform type and version, Internet Service Provider (ISP) and (for users of our service through a mobile device) Unique Device Identifier, operating system, referral source/exit pages, length of visit, page views, website navigation, date/time stamp information and details like the number and location of (mouse) clicks on a given page, mouse movements, scrolling activity and the (search) words you use and the text you type while being on and using our website); 
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us; 
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters; and 
  * any other information that you choose to send to us.

We may also ask you to complete surveys and/or provide feedback on our website or services (including via carefully selected third party service provider), although you do not have to respond to them. If you do respond to them, our third party service providers will provide us with the results. 

### (2) Information about other people

If you provide information to us about any person other than yourself, you must ensure that they understand how their information will be used and that you are authorised to disclose it to us, and consent its use on their behalf, before doing so. 

### (3) Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We use both "session" cookies and "short-term" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies for such purposes as to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the short-term cookies for such purposes as to enable our website to recognise you when you visit. 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Short-term cookies will remain stored on your computer for a period of 30 days. 

In addition to this, we use web analytics services provided by Google, Inc ("Google"). Google use cookies, to help analyse how visitors use our website. The information generated by the cookie about the use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity for us and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

We also work with advertising partners to serve ads that we believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partners may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) . 

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. More information about cookies can be found at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Below is a detailed list of the cookies that we use on this website, including those cookies that are essential for the website to operate. 

** Category/ Type  **

| 

** Cookie Name  **

| 

** Purpose  **

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
** Our Cookies  **

|    
  
Vital site functionality 

Session 

| 

Lateroomsprofile 

| 

This cookie notes customer data such as your preferred language/currency/country and it is critical for the website to work. 

|    
  
Vital site functionality 

Session 

| 

Search 

| 

This cookie ensure your search preferences are stored so that the website remembers what you are searching for, such as number of nights, children, adults, arrival date, etc. and it is critical for the website to work. 

|    
  
Site Analytics 

Session 

| 

ASP.NET_SessionId 

| 

This cookie retains the your current session so that you can return to the website if you encounter a browser issue and then are still be able to make a booking. 

|    
  
Vital site functionality 

Short-Term 

| 

Partner Cookies 

| 

These cookies are used to identify which partner has referred a user when they have arrived on the website via a link from a partner site.  This cookie is placed by the partner site prior to arriving on the website.  This enables us to identify referral customers and remunerate partners and is vital to the functioning of the affiliate referral program. 

|    
  
** Third Party Analytics and Other Cookies **

|    
  
** Category  **

| 

** Third Party  **

| 

** Purpose and Further Information  **

|    
  
Site Analytics 

| 

Google 

| 

These cookies monitor the traffic volumes to the website to allow us to understand how the website is working and fix any problems.  This ensures that the website is fully functional and optimised to create the best possible user experience. 

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please see Google's privacy policy at:  [ http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html ](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) or visit [ http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout ](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) . 

|    
  
Site Analytics 

| 

Tealeaf 

| 

These are cookies that are used to analyse a user’s actions across our website during single and multiple visits so we can understand how you are using the website. This provides us with information to ensure the best possible user experience  . 

|    
  
Site Analytics 

| 

Maxymiser 

| 

These are cookies that are used to analyse a user’s actions and behaviours on our website through conversion optimization solutions so we can understand how you are using the website. This provides us with information to ensure the best possible user experience. 

|    
  
Bookmarking & sharing 

| 

AddThis 

| 

These are cookies are used to enable sharing of content and they also measure content impacts across various social network streams. 

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please see AddThis’ privacy policy at  [ http://www.addthis.com/privacy ](http://www.addthis.com/privacy)

|    
  
** Third Party Marketing Cookies  **

|    
  
** Category  **

| 

** Third Party  **

| 

** Purpose and Further Information  **

|  |    
  
Marketing - Search 

| 

Efficient Frontier 

| 

These third party cookies allow us to monitor the effectiveness of our search marketing campaigns on Google, Yahoo and MSN. This means we can make the adverts more useful to you by providing you with content that is timely and relevant. 

To

opt-out of receiving **** these cookies please follow this link: [ http://www.efrontier.com/optout-page ](http://www.efrontier.com/optout-page)  

|  |    
  
Marketing - Targeted 

| 

Criteo 

| 

These third party cookies allow us to deliver adverts to you (after you have left the Sitelate) that show the best hotel deals for the locations you have been searching for.  This means that you will be shown deals that you may have missed without having to search the site again.  This is called online behavioural advertising, a common online advertising practice and does not collect any personal data. 

To

opt-out of receiving **** these cookies please follow this link: [ http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy/opt-out ](http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy/opt-out)  

|  |    
  
Marketing – Display Banners 

| 

These third party cookies allow us to monitor the effectiveness of our online banner marketing campaigns on Doubleclick (Google), Yahoo, Xaxis, Yahoo, MSN and Flashtalking amongst others. This means we can make the adverts more useful to you by providing you with content that is timely and relevant. We also use these cookies to ensure we are not serving a high volume of ads to you. 

To

opt-out of receiving **** these cookies please follow these links:  [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx)     
[ http://www.flashtalking.com/intelligent.html ](http://www.flashtalking.com/intelligent.html)  (follow the link in the bottom right)   
[ http://www.xaxis.com/uk ](http://www.xaxis.com/uk)  (follow the link in the bottom right)   

You can also

opt-out of receiving **** other third party marketing cookies by following this link:  [ http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices ](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices)

|  |    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
|    
  
Some of our Website pages and HTML-formatted e-mail newsletters may use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregate statistics about website usage. A Web beacon is an electronic image, called a single-pixel (1x1) or clear GIF and are used like cookies to recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as your cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. 

### (4) Using your personal information

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. 

We may use your personal information to:

  * manage and administer the website;
  * improve your browsing experience by personalising the website; 
  * enable your use of the services available on the website including providing you with login in details so you may access details of your bookings; 
  * manage, administer, mediate and contract the services offered by us via the website and/or our call centre; 
  * manage, administer, mediate and contract your bookings made through the website and/or our call-centre; 
  * send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications including communications about any important changes to the website and/or surveys or feedback we (or our appointed third party service providers on our behalf) may ask you to complete; 
  * send you email notifications confirming your bookings made via the website and/or our call centre and any other email notifications you have specifically requested; 
  * contact you by post, telephone or e-communication (including email and SMS) with information on our latest news and updates including details of our, or our carefully selected third parties’, goods and services, special offers, discounts or promotions, details of new products or services and forthcoming events or competitions offered by us, unless you have opted out of receiving such information by ticking the relevant box on the booking form (you can also inform us at any time if you do not wish to receive e-communications by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in e-communication); 
  * provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; 
  * deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website, your bookings and/or the services offered by us or our suppliers; 
  * to analyse and improve the services offered on our website and to provide you with the most user-friendly navigation experience. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate for marketing and strategic development purposes; 
  * send you an email inviting you to leave a guest review on the website following your stay; and 
  * deliver marketing and advertising to you that show services and deals that we think you will be interested in including via targeted advertising on third party websites and/or platforms. 

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us. 

We may monitor, record, store and use any telephone, email or other communication with you for monitoring purposes, in order to check any instructions given to us by you, for staff training purposes, for crime prevention and to improve the quality of our customer service. 

We will not provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing by such third party unless you have provided your express consent by activating the “opt-in” option on the website or for example where you have elected to participate in a promotion offered via a third party on our website. In such cases, we shall only transfer to the third party adequate, relevant and not excessive personal data (name, address and email addresses) so you will be able to receive direct marketing material from such third party. You can inform us at any time if you no longer wish for your details to be disclosed to such third party and we will no longer disclose your information. The relevant third party will show their contact information in their marketing material and we have no control over such third party marketing material, therefore we disclaim any kind of liability that may arise from such third party marketing material. 

You expressly agree to such uses of personal information.

### (5) Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers, partners or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy or whom we have appointed to process information on our behalf or manage aspects of our website. Please note we must disclose information about you to the relevant suppliers of your travel arrangements. 

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

  * to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  * in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; 
  * in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); 
  * to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling; and 
  * to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information. 

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. 

You expressly agree to such disclosures of personal information. 

### (6) International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we and/or our suppliers operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area (EEA), in particular where your booking destination is outside the EEA. Please note, if we cannot pass this information to the relevant accommodation and/or service providers, whether in the EEA or not, we cannot provide the services to you. 

Information may be transferred to companies contracted by us to perform services in connection with this website who are based outside the EEA including in the United States, where such organisations have signed up to the US Safe Harbour Principles and/or contracts providing an adequate level of protection have been signed. 

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website as a review will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.  We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others. 

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information. 

### (7) Security of your personal information

Please note that, in accordance with European personal data protection laws, we will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. 

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website). 

### (8) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.  Your continued use of the website shall constitute your agreement and acceptance of the changes to this policy. 

### (9) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to: 

  * the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00); and
  * the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address). 

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law. 

You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes. 

### (10) Third party websites

The website contains, and our email communications may contain, links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites including use of cookies on such third party websites and you should prefer to the third party’s privacy policy for more information. 

### (11) Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. 

### (12) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please contact us [here](http://www.laterooms.com.au/en/static/ContactUs.mvc) or by post to Late Rooms Ltd, The Peninsula, Victoria Place, Manchester, M4 4FB. 

### (13) Data controller

The data controller responsible in respect of the information collected on this website is Late Rooms Limited, whose registered office address is TUI Travel House, Crawley Business Quarter, Fleming Way, Crawley, West Sussex, RH10 9QL. 

Our data protection registration number is Z8168511.

Updated January 2015
